<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="10"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[             ]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ ROCKA will always provide the best cost effective solution to our customer’s challenges for them to be more competitive in the market.
LATINAMERICAN PRESENCE
A Mexican company with more than 25 years of combined experience, with presence in Latin America offering warehousing, new technologies, shipping solutions and technical expertise to electronic and mechanical industries.
Global business experience
More than 25 years of combined experience
Full understanding
of Latin American market
Active members of SMTA
Local Storage in USA, Mexico, Brazil & Argentina
Local technical support
OUR PRINCIPALS
]]></page><page Index="3" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Printer Pick & Place Reflow Oven Wave Solder Selective Solder Router Conformal Coating Rework Final Assembly
                                                                                          SOLUTIONS
         ]]></page><page Index="4" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  www. ROCKA solutions.com
]]></page><page Index="5" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[    Pet Inspection Templates Stencil Stencil Design Smt Clean Roll Smt Adhesive Roll Smt Wipes Solder Paste Adhesive / Epoxy Axarel 2200 – Cleaner Inside Printer Stencil Cleaner Misprint Cleaner Solder Preform Splice Tape Nozzles Nozzles Cleaner Cleansafe Smt Cleaner High Temperature Oil
                                                                                                                              SMT
  PRINTER PICK & PLACE REFLOW OVEN
WAVE SOLDER SELECTIVE SOLDER ROUTER CONFORMAL COATING REWORK
]]></page><page Index="6" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  www. ROCKA solutions.com
]]></page><page Index="7" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Kapton Tape Kapton Dots Kapton Custom Shapes Masking Dots Masking Tape Pet Tape Pet Dots Solder Alloy Solder Preforms Fluxes Solder Dross Reduction Powder Cleansafe Pallet Cleaning Pallets Carriers Pet Inspection Templates Flux For Nozzles (Pre-thinned) Drill Bit Brushes Work Holders Conformal Coating Cleansafe Conformal Coating Cleaner Mixers Fixing Silicone Fluoro-coating Dispensing Nozzles Mixer Nozzles Potting Encapsulation Thermal Conductivity Hotmelt Coredwire Iron Tips Flux Pen Paste Flux Kapton Tape Kapton Dots Tip Thinner Tip Scouter / Sponges
                                                                                                                                                     BACK-END
                PRINTER PICK & PLACE REFLOW OVEN WAVE SOLDER SELECTIVE SOLDER ROUTER CONFORMAL COATING REWORK
]]></page><page Index="8" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[   www. ROCKA solutions.com
]]></page><page Index="9" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  We call it High Presicion
Cleaning
SMT CLEANER
PALLET CLEANER
CONFORMAL
COATING CLEANER
  BY
          Biodegradable Rinsing Optional Non-Flammable
Low Foaming
Rust Inhibiting
Ultra Low-Odor Aluminum Compatible Ready to USE
Non corrosive
VOC free
NPE/APE Free
Phosphate free
Glycol Free
Corrosion Inhibition
Proven Cleaning Ability Safe on Metals, Composites Long Bath Life
Easy Water Rinsing
No Additives Required
Low Foaming
Removes SMT Adhesive
Fast Dry Times
Replaces Acetone, IPA, MEK, MPK Powerful Cleaning Ability
USDA Certified Biobased Low Surface Residue
With a process driven, solutions-oriented focus, Vantage is a leading global supplier of process cleaning solutions, coating removers and other surface treatments for aerospace, electronics circuit assembly and other high-reliability industrial markets.
       CleanSafe
MAINTENANCE
 ]]></page><page Index="10" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ www.rockasolutions.com
]]></page></pages></Search>